hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Byakugan!
Caught 'em!
All right! All right!
I'll drag Sasuke back without fail!
Naruto! Hate to tell you this
but I'm gonna demonstrate
my new Jutsu right here!
Me too!
Don't be so hasty.
As soon as preparations have been made
to implement my strategy...
we'll make direct contact
with the target!
It looks like they haven't
noticed us yet.
Huh? Sasuke isn't there.
It appears that...
he's inside that "coffin."
What's this?
I poked the bush for kicks
and out comes not even a snake
but just two bugs.
Hey, wait a minute! Wait!
We didn't come here to fight.
We just came here to negotiate!
Huh, then...
What are they?!
There's no point
to that Smoke Bomb.
You can't run away from me.
It's string that's thinner and stronger
than wire that you can hardly see.
My string is placed all over this place.
Damn.
Those two types of wires
on the trap were on purpose...
It was actually a triple trap.
Damn.
Didn't think they had one
with such ability in the group...
You will be...!
What's going on...? My body...
Nice! Kiba, Shikamaru!
Shadow Possession Jutsu succeeded!
But... There is one with
ability like this too.
Thanks for getting caught so nicely
in my strategy.
Damn... But...
I have this kind of ability too.
Where did it come from?
Earth Style Barrier!
Earth Dome Prison!
Suddenly a Fight
Among The Group?!
Shikamaru's Squad
in Big Danger
Damn!
Where is this?
Inside of that big guy's barrier.
Damn!
These guys are mine.
I want to recover as much as possible.
Once you're done eating,
catch up with us,
we're going ahead.
Come quickly.
Let us out! You!
Be quiet, Naruto!
From the looks of it,
it just looks like a dirt wall...
It's their Jutsu,
there must be some kind of trap.
I don't know what it's made of
but we're just going to
have to tear this wall down!
Even though
it's dangerous to be careless,
it's actually more dangerous
to remain silent here.
Tunneling Fang!
The wall is restoring itself...
Hey...
I saw that.
Let us out!
It's not just a dirt wall after all.
Byakugan!
Th-This is...
What is it? What's happening?
This is bad.
Chakra's getting sucked up...
Damn... I didn't expect that
they would just keep us in the barrier
but I didn't predict that
they would suck our Chakra either.
Man. How dare they!
Let us out of here already!
I've had a good amount of Chakra.
Thank you for the meal.
I feel like my body energy
is being sucked out.
It won't be good if
we stay like this here, Shikamaru.
It was careless to get caught
before we even figured out
our enemy's powers.
On top of all that... inside here.
Damn! I'm going to make an air hole
before all my Chakra is gone!
Akamaru!
The Food Pills!
Human Mimicry Ninja Art!
And for me
Beast Mimicry Ninja Art!
Fang Over Fang!
All right! Good going Kiba.
It's useless...
Damn! It starts to restore
the moment it's hit.
Same with the ground.
At this rate we won't be able to
keep up for another ten minutes.
We'll lose all our Chakra
and be totally annihilated...
I can't use the Rasengan that
requires extremely difficult Chakra control
especially in a place like this
that sucks the Chakra out of us.
Damn!
Hey, I want you to listen to me!
I want to talk to your leader.
We won't go after Sasuke anymore
so let us out of here!
Hey...
Shikamaru, what are you saying?
Pleading for your life,
how interesting...
But you guys are my prey
I can't let you out.
Then... just let me out on my own.
This battle...
is such a pain.
You! Do you know
what you're saying?
Shut up Kiba, be quiet...
What?!
A split in the group, huh?
Seems like you're the leader but...
I didn't think you would be
the only one begging for your life!
You really see a human's true nature
when one is pushed to the edge of death.
You're such a low-life creature
you're not qualified to be responsible
for the lives of your platoon members.
I've saved the most
important thing for last...
To abandon Sasuke and
to even sell out on your own platoon...
Is that what it means
to be a Chunin of the Leaf?
Sasuke is a Shinobi of
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
He is a comrade!
Therefore, I will put my life on the line
to help him!
That's the way of the Leaf Village.
Someone like you deserves to die...
I won't let you out.
Shikamaru! I believed in you
but now I've lost confidence in you!
Let's take this outside!
Hey, we can't get out!
You fool!
That's why we're in this situation!
What do you mean by "fool"?
I'm just speaking the truth, fool!
Oh! You said "fool" again!
Everybody be quiet for a second!
Choji?
Now he's squatting down.
What is he thinking?
Hey! Why are you eating snacks
all of a sudden?!
Choji binge eats when he gets upset...
Jeez, another useless guy.
It can't be helped!
In this case Shadow Clone...!
Stop it.
The enemy's Chakra is placed
all over that wall.
Even if you are able to scratch it
the wall will restore itself right away.
In other words, it's useless
unless we can attack it
with a Taijutsu that has enough power
to destroy this wall with one blow.
Somebody that has a Taijutsu
with greater destructive power than mine
would be Choji but...
At this rate...
Damn, what do we do!
Neji... I'm sorry but can you use
the rest of the Chakra you have
to observe the wall behind you
and the wall behind Choji?
I got it.
Shikamaru! You be quiet!
Naruto!
You still don't understand?!
Remember what Shikamaru said
when he gathered everyone!
Even I can't just sit back and be lazy.
Because I'm responsible
for your lives.
Choji, don't raise your voice
too much from here.
Kiba, dent that wall
behind Neji and Choji again!
Y-Yeah...
Huh! I don't fully understand
what's going on
but I'll go wild one more time!
Tunneling Fang!
Huh! No matter how hard you try
it's useless!
Huh, I see...
It's over there.
Neji!
Mark that spot with the Kunai Knife.
Choji, are you ready?!
Okay! Any time!
All right, let's do this.
What's happening?!
Like I said earlier,
the wall's surface is planted with Chakra.
But even this tough wall could have
an area that has a thin layer of Chakra.
That is what Shikamaru speculated.
How... How did you get all of that?
Think about what happened earlier.
Because he noticed that
there were areas that restored quickly
and others that didn't so quickly
when Kiba and Akamaru attacked
the wall surface.
In other words, he guessed that
those areas that didn't restore quickly
probably have a thin layer
of Chakra.
On top of all that
by cleverly talking to the enemy
he figured out the position
of the enemy outside of the wall.
He guessed that
the wall furthest from the enemy
probably had the thinnest point
of Chakra
so that's what he wanted to confirm.
That's what it is, correct?
I see, in order to trick the enemy
you must trick your friends first.
I didn't see that there was
such a plan behind that conversation.
Then Choji realized the plan
and the reason why he was eating
was to replenish his Chakra.
These two...
They haven't been working together
as a team all these years for nothing.
I'm depending on you, Choji.
Yeah!
Expansion Jutsu!
All right, let's go!
Human Boulder!
What?!
Choji... You are awesome after all!
GET UP aa sumimasen
get up! oh, I'm sorry
goku tama ni boku tama ni
once in a long while, once in a while
yume ni yabureru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person broken by dreams
yama no you ni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
clinging to God, clinging to Buddha
sugari naiteru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person crying
yama no you ni mieru
danran dansu de RANDEBUU
rendezvous with a happy dance circle
ore shouri no poozu da randaran
this is my victory pose, round and around
SHEIKU SHEIKU SHEIKU sagasou janai
shake shake shake let's look
owaranai baibai no RIZUMU de
with a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
yama no you ni mieru
Huh? What are you saying
all of a sudden, Choji!
There's no way that's possible!
But Choji is right.
If we keep lagging we won't be able
to catch up with Sasuke.
But still...
Don't worry. I have an idea.
Choji, are you possibly thinking...
Do you have a plan or something?
Yeah.
Hey! Choji!
That's right!
I have that secret weapon of mine!
Next time:
"Full Power! Burn, Choji!"
I'm the one who will defeat that guy!